KAZUKO BAYNTON

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

⊗ kazukobaynton.com ♥ Vancouver Island, BC in kazbaynton ♠ Kaz1022

SUMMARY

Full stack developer graduated from web developing bootcamp at Lighthouse Labs. Specializes in JavaScript, HTML + CSS, React, Node.js, SQL, Ruby on Rails. Professional strengths include a flexible mind-set, patience, strong written and verbal communication and teamwork skills, and efficient time management. I enjoy creating accessible products that are easy to use with a clean design.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES Iav

Javascript, Ruby, HTML, CSS, SQL

FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES

NodeJS, React, Ajax, Express, EJS, jQuery, Rails, Active Record,

Bootstrap, SASS

SYSTEMS & DATABASES

PostgreSQL, Git

TESTING

Jest, Storybook, Cypress

PROJECTS

AN AUTHOR'S WEBSITE

Aug. 2022 to Sept. 2022

A static website for Author Brian Baynton to showcase his work. Deployed on Netlify.

Tech Stack: React, Framer Motion, Swiper, HTML, CSS and SASS

ARPEGGIO Aug. 2022 to Aug. 2022

A web app where a user can post a music session, and others see the available spots and apply to attend the session. Final Group Project at Lighthouse Labs.

Tech Stack: React, HTML, CSS, Styled-Component, React Bootstrap, Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL and Twilio API

LIGHTHOUSE MARKETPLACE

May 2022 to May 2022

A simple web app where a user can list multiple items for sale, find the items you want to buy and easily contact sellers. The first group project at LighthouseLabs.

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, SASS, JS, jQuery, PostgreSQL, Node and Express

EDUCATION

Lighthouse Labs

Jan. 2022 to Aug. 2022

Diploma Web Development

Nanzan University

Apr. 2007 to Mar. 2011

BA French Studies

EMPLOYMENT

Personal Trainer/Yoga Instructor · Raincity Boxing Studio · Vancouver BC

Jan. 2019 to Apr. 2022

- Created customized programs based on individual or group needs
- Collaborated with clients to meet scheduling needs
- Communicated with the team in order to increase overall gym satisfaction and to meet the company goal

Customer Service Representative · Air Canada · Vancouver BC

Sept. 2017 to Mar. 2020

- Worked in agile environment with constantly changing priorities
- Handled check-ins, boardings, arrivals of flights, demonstrating strong time-management skills and an ability to work autonomously
- Solved problems both externally and internally with constant communication